Hello, Pei Ning.
We've been waiting for you for a long time.
Grandpa.
My two big grandsons.
Grandpa,
how come you have time to visit today?
happy birthday.
Today is my birthday?
Look at me, I'm getting senile.
I even forgot my own birthday.
Yes, I
specially saved money for a long time
to buy you this liquor.
Take a look.
My Ningning is really thoughtful.
Good.
Let me see
what my older brother got.
Grandpa,
happy birthday.
Pei Song,
how could you buy such an expensive gift?
It's not expensive, I made it by hand.
You made it?
How is it? Do you like it?
My grandson is amazing.
This craftsmanship
is so exquisite.
Of course I like it.
It's a gift from my eldest grandson,
how could I not like it?
All right, I'll accept it.
Thank you.
Why do you have these?
So our current research direction is
to feed massive user data to AI
and train more models,
then build a
marriage and relationship matching platform.
But I'd like to ask,
how do you view the future trend of AI?
What about its development trend?
It will definitely be the future direction and trend.
But with strong capabilities now,
how big can its future scale actually get?
A trillion-dollar market, I suppose.
Actually, it can't get that big.
You see,
there are a few trends.
Marriage e-commerce,
everything you can think of and use.
I think it's all doable.
I didn't quite get it.
Can you explain it to me again?
You can actually listen to me.
I've already summarized it all here.
He explained it very clearly.
We don't need you at all, okay?
Let me reiterate.
Our current research direction is
to feed massive user emotional data to AI,
train various models,
put them into the market,
and establish a marriage matching system.
Fellow students, when we go outdoor exploring,
the most important gear includes
trekking poles.
Trekking poles are very important.
They can ensure that during our climb,
we save our strength.
And our
climbing rope.
How do we use the climbing rope?
Wrap one end around our waist,
and tie the other end to the carabiner.
It is very sturdy.
So when we encounter danger,
we must act according to our capabilities.
There is another essential piece of equipment,
which is our
first aid kit.
During mountain climbing,
bumps and bruises are inevitable.
So we can pack some alcohol,
iodine, and band-aids inside.
Next up
is our hiking backpack.
Inside it,
you can pack some items.
Stop playing it.
Dating e-commerce.
Everything that girls think of
and use.
Stop.
Actually, you could say
I think dating isn't
Stop playing it.
It's not about you.
Stop talking.
He made it very clear,
and I understood it long ago.
Pei Ning,
you are so lucky.
You have such a capable brother.
You're practically Pei Song's mini-me.
Stop.
But the brother is still a bit more capable.
Pei Song is really good to you.
He gives in to you on everything.
In the future, the company's affairs will be left to your brother.
Stop playing it.
Just do whatever you want.
Stop.
Don't feel burdened.
It's okay, little brother.
Your brother is here.
You don't need to do anything.
I will protect you well.
Why hasn't it stopped yet?
Stop talking.
Stop.
Don't feel burdened.
I will protect you well.
Stop.
Enough.
Make him stop.
Why should you protect me?
I'm clearly stronger than you.
I'm stronger than you.
Pull yourself together.
We'll help you surpass Pei Song.
Shiya.
This AI system
is finally almost complete.
Then why,
why are you marrying my brother?
Do you also think
my brother is better than me?
Do you know how hard
I worked to develop this system?
You bastard.
This is an outrage.
You disgrace
our family.
No, Grandpa.
Listen to me.
It's not what you think.
I should never have
brought you home.
Grandpa, listen to me.
Get out of here.
Get out.
Grandpa, listen to me.
Get out!
Can you just listen to me?
You're killing me.
I'd rather die than be saved by you.
Since I was little,
my brother has gotten all the good things.
Wasn't he also adopted by you?
No matter how well I do, it's useless.
I just don't understand,
why you are so biased.
Shiya.
What's wrong?
Open it and see.
Your birthday is coming up.
I didn't know what you'd like,
so I picked out a watch for you.
Shiya,
I miss you so much.
Don't we see each other every day?
There are some things
I don't know how to explain to you.
But once I handle all of this,
I will tell you everything.
Until then,
you must be careful of Pei Ning.
Don't be alone with him.
Pei Ning.
Hello, Xiaoning.
What's wrong?
Hey, brother.
Bad news.
Grandpa fainted.